[
  {
    "questionNo": "Q1",
    "question": "Cindy bought 8 packs of stickers for $24. What is the cost of 1 pack of stickers?",
    "options": [
      "$2",
      "$3",
      "$4",
      "$5"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q2",
    "question": "Ben and Cindy bought 9 notebooks for $45. What is the cost of 1 notebook?",
    "options": [
      "$2",
      "$3",
      "$4",
      "$5"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q3",
    "question": "Cindy bought 9 erasers for $36. What is the cost of 1 eraser?",
    "options": [
      "$4",
      "$6",
      "$8",
      "$10"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q4",
    "question": "If 1 backpack costs $9, what is the cost of 6 backpacks?",
    "options": [
      "$45",
      "$48",
      "$52",
      "$54"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q5",
    "question": "If 1 water bottle costs $14, what is the cost of 7 water bottles?",
    "options": [
      "$98",
      "$88",
      "$80",
      "$78"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q6",
    "question": "If 1 set of crayons costs $4, what is the cost of 13 sets of crayons?",
    "options": [
      "$50",
      "$52",
      "$54",
      "$56"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q7",
    "question": "Ben saw that 10 lunchboxes cost $60. What is the cost of 1 lunchbox?",
    "options": [
      "$4",
      "$5",
      "$6",
      "$7"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q8",
    "question": "They purchased 11 glue sticks for $55. What is the cost of 1 glue stick?",
    "options": [
      "$3",
      "$4",
      "$5",
      "$6"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q9",
    "question": "If 1 ruler costs $3, what is the cost of 12 rulers?",
    "options": [
      "$30",
      "$32",
      "$34",
      "$36"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q10",
    "question": "Cindy bought 15 colored pencils for $60. What is the cost of 1 colored pencil?",
    "options": [
      "$4",
      "$6",
      "$5",
      "$3"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  }
]
